[SHELDON MOANING]
Sure. I'll pick you up in 10 minutes.
(Howard:)Gentlemen, adieu.
I thought we were gonna play
"Halo" tonight.
What am I supposed to do?
(Howard:)There's a woman out there
anxious to have sex with me.
(Howard:)You understand, right?
(Penny:)No, not at all.
(Howard:)Nevertheless, I must depart.
By the way, did I tell you Leslie pulled
strings and got me on the trip to Geneva...
...to check out the CERN super collider?
(Leonard:)That's not fair.
You're not even a physicist.
(Howard:)There are two ways
of looking at this...
- Get out.
- Bye.
(Leslie:)You're improving.
(Leonard:)Thank you.
(Howard:)It helps when I get to practice
with a real woman.
(Leslie:)Hey, listen.
Saturday, my sister's getting married.
(Leslie:)I want you to come with me.
It's black tie.
(Howard:)Yeah, gee, I'd really rather not.